[microphone feedback]
[♪ opening theme music playing]
FLEX X COP 2
CHARACTERS, PLACES, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
ALL CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS
FILMED IN A SAFE ENVIRONMENT
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
Thanks.
These photos...
They're the victims.
Jo Nayeong.
Choi Yeongmin.
Kim Heejun.
Jo Nayeong and Choi Yeongmin
were amateur models,
and they went missing the day
after they met Yu Seongwon.
So I was watching Yu Seongwon.
SEPTEMBER 14, 2021
[knock on car window]
You're a detective, right?
Can I get in?
What did Seongwon do?
Why do you ask?
Because I'm curious.
I'm really close with him.
[inhales sharply]
But how should I put this?
Sometimes he seems a little crazy.
The other day, while having a drink,
he said something strange.
What did he say?
That he wanted to use
a corpse as his model.
He said if the model moves
while he's feeling inspired,
he wants to kill them.
I heard his models disappeared.
Is it true?
Can I have your number?
GANGHA POLICE
DETECTIVE JOO HYERA
I'll let you know
if he does anything suspicious.
Wait.
It's too dangerous. Stay away from him.
I've got good instincts.
I'll keep you updated.
[Hyera] Kim Heejun
went missing after that.
And Yu Seongwon moved to the UK.
I believe Yu Seongwon made that piece
after killing Kim Heejun,
to put his murder on display.
He wants to show off
that he's the killer.
ECSTASY
A BREATHLESS FALL
CLIMAX
LIGHT SCATTERED ACROSS THE UNIVERSE
I couldn't pinpoint
where the other victims had been murdered,
but Kim Heejun likely died
in a field of reeds.
DISSOLUTION
THE SILENCE OF WHISPERING REEDS
[♪ tense, suspenseful music playing]
He left a clue in his artwork on purpose.
Because he's become certain
he'd never get caught.
[Isoo sighs softly]
DALSEONG WETLAND
YEONGSAN RIVER GARDEN
Is that why you collected these?
[Hyera] Yes.
GAPCHEON WETLAND
I need to find out
where the murder happened
to at least recover the body.
Will you help me?
[♪ tense, suspenseful music continues]
EPISODE 9
[Isoo sighs softly]
[chuckles] Young Master.
Gosh, you're still calling me
"Young Master."
Have you been well? It's been a while.
It's good to see you again.
Seongwon is inside, isn't he?
Yes. Please go ahead.
[♪ gripping, suspenseful music playing]
[Seongwon] Oh!
Isoo!
Hey, what are you doing here?
You didn't even call.
I was just passing by.
You missed me, didn't you? [chuckles]
What's that? A gift?
Yeah.
It's the whiskey I made.
Wait here a second.
Mr. Hwang!
Do we have any fruit?
[♪ gripping, foreboding music playing]
[♪ music fades]
[exhales contentedly]
Wow. Did you really make this?
Of course I did.
This is a work of art.
- Cheers.
- [chuckles]
[clink]
By the way, that piece there.
What does it mean?
[Seongwon] Mmm?
[Isoo] What's with the pebbles
and why stick the reed in?
I just don't get it.
Why do you ask?
[♪ tense, suspenseful music playing]
It's a secret.
You...
[exclaims incredulously] You're acting
like I know nothing about art again.
Forget it. Don't tell me
if you don't want to.
[chuckles] No, it's fine.
I'll make an exception for you.
[Seongwon] Mmm...
For me,
there are moments I could never forget.
Moments I can recall
down to every last detail.
The sunlight that day,
the smell of the air,
it's all in my head.
The moment I first met you is one of them.
[♪ music fades]
Me?
At the gathering?
You don't remember, do you?
We met way before that.
When I was just a kid.
I've liked you ever since then.
That piece
is a memory of one of those moments.
[♪ ominous music playing]
In a field of reeds in early winter,
I'm walking forward,
stepping over the gravel.
It was drizzling that day.
[Heejun] Seongwon.
I made that piece to remember that moment.
[♪ music fades]
I met Seongwon yesterday.
What do you think?
I don't know if he's the real killer,
but here.
I took it from that sculpture.
[♪ tense, suspenseful music playing]
By the way,
there was a kiln in his studio.
A kiln?
If he burned the bodies there...
We won't find any DNA.
[sighs]
I'll look into this first.
Also,
he said it was raining that day.
The day he found inspiration
for that piece.
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
[♪ gripping, foreboding music playing]
JUYEON ARTS HIGH SCHOOL
THIRD-YEAR DANCE STUDENT
MOON SEYEON
[♪ music fades]
[♪ percussive folk music playing]
[blade swooshing]
[♪ music stops]
[♪ soft, suspenseful music playing]
[♪ music turns ominous]
[♪ music swells, fades]
[exhales softly]
[sniffles]
[♪ percussive folk music playing]
[blade swooshing]
[♪ music turns suspenseful]
[panting]
[girl, weakly] Please... help me.
[♪ ominous music playing]
[sword clatters]
[Seyeon] Don't come any closer.
Stay away from me!
[screaming]
Go away!
[♪ music swells, fades]
[scream echoes, fades]
[students chattering]
DANCE STUDIO 1
[all scream]
[♪ tense, suspenseful music playing]
Oh, my God.
[students whispering anxiously]
Why aren't you girls going in?
[student] Ms. Jeong.
What?
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[Juhee gasps]
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
[siren blaring]
[brakes squeal]
[siren stops blaring]
[♪ tense, suspenseful music playing]
- [Isoo] How did this happen?
- [♪ music fades]
Let's check if anyone's been in or out.
Got it.
[sighs softly]
[♪ soft melancholy music playing]
- [audio distorts]
- [slow, muffled thuds]
[high-pitched tone droning, intensifies]
- [high-pitched tone fades]
- [audio normalizes]
[♪ soft melancholy music continues]
Please have a look.
[dispenser clicks]
[exhales heavily]
[Isoo breathing heavily]
[Hyera] What's wrong?
[panting] Uh...
I was just thirsty.
[exhales heavily]
- [continues panting]
- [♪ music fades]
[knock at door]
We're from Gangha Police Station.
Who is the deceased student?
Her name is Moon Seyeon.
I'm her homeroom teacher.
When did you last see her?
Uh...
[♪ tense, ticking music playing]
When school let out at 5:00 p.m.
But
she said she was going to rehearse
in the practice room from 9:00.
Nine o'clock at night?
Yes.
Is the practice room
used at night as well?
Uh...
Seyeon is the lead dancer
in the arts festival,
so she was allowed to use it anytime.
Allowed by whom?
The principal.
Seyeon was personally instructed
by the principal.
Do the teachers stay late
at school with her?
No, we go home for the day.
The principal sometimes stays behind
to help Seyeon with practice,
but she left early yesterday.
Then who is at school late at night?
The security guard on night duty.
- Check with the security office.
- [both] Okay.
[♪ music swells, fades]
[♪ gripping, suspenseful music playing]
GRAND PRIZE
AWARD CERTIFICATE
JUYEON ARTS HIGH SCHOOL
[♪ music fades]
[knock at door]
2025 JUYEON ARTS HIGH SCHOOL ARTS FESTIVAL
[Isoo] We're from Gangha Police Station.
[gasps]
PRINCIPAL OF JUYEON ARTS HIGH SCHOOL
JEONG JOOHEE
Aren't you the dancer Jeong Joohee?
You know me?
Of course. I even went
to your performance in New York.
It's an honor.
[chuckles softly]
She's famous.
A living legend of Korean dance.
[chuckles softly] You're too kind.
It's all in the past.
This is my team leader.
She doesn't get out much.
- She knows nothing about the arts.
- I'm Joo Hyera with Gangha Police.
Uh, I'm Jin Isoo.
Right, yes.
Please have a seat.
[Isoo exhales in awe]
CERTIFICATE OF APPOINTMENT
Oh, so you became a principal.
I had some health issues.
Now I devote my time to teaching students.
Oh. They're lucky
to be learning from a legend.
[chuckles softly] Not at all.
I appreciate your kind words.
We're here because of Moon Seyeon.
You know what happened, right?
[breath trembles] Yes.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[exhales heavily]
I was so shocked
at the studio this morning.
We heard you personally instructed Seyeon.
She was a very talented student.
She had the potential
to become a great dancer.
Was Seyeon at school
by herself last night?
[Juhee] Yes.
She was scheduled
to practice on her own yesterday.
The arts festival is
just around the corner,
so she worked very hard,
practicing every day without fail.
[Hyera breathes deeply]
Was there anyone
who didn't get along with Seyeon?
Teacher or student, anyone at all.
I'm not sure.
She wasn't a difficult person,
and she was an outgoing, sweet girl.
She was the lead dancer of the festival,
and she was personally taught by you.
Someone might have been jealous of her.
That happens all the time.
All my students
are ambitious and passionate.
Being jealous and competitive
is part of how you grow, isn't it?
That's true.
But killing someone for that reason?
There's no one like that at our school.
[♪ music fades]
I was on duty yesterday.
I went home this morning,
but came back after I got the call.
Did you see
the deceased student last night?
Yes, she came in around 9:00 p.m.
[♪ gripping, suspenseful music playing]
She's been coming every night.
Did you notice anything unusual?
Like anyone following her?
No, she went inside
and I locked the gate right away.
Was that the last time you saw her?
I last saw her
when I was making my round at 10:00 p.m.
She was practicing alone.
[♪ muffled percussive folk music plays]
Did you notice anything unusual then?
Like I said, no.
Did you check inside all the classrooms?
Well, not really,
but all the classrooms were locked.
There really was no one there.
I have no idea how this happened.
[♪ music fades]
Could you copy
all the security footage onto this?
[softly] Sure.
What's going to happen to me?
Will I get in trouble for this?
[♪ suspenseful, pulsating music playing]
Why would you worry about that?
I'm just worried
I might get blamed for this.
You'll be fine
if you've done nothing wrong.
[sighs wearily]
CHANGING ROOM
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
- Let's visit the victim's home first.
- Okay.
Oh.
- Mmm. Delicious.
- [Isoo] It's bungeoppang.
I've wanted to try that.
Have you never had bungeoppang?
They don't sell it near my place.
- [chuckles softly] Go get some.
- Really?
Nice!
- Be quick.
- Okay, got it.
Where do you buy those?
Where's Isoo going?
To get bungeoppang.
- He's never had it before.
- What?
[scoffs] He surprisingly hasn't tried
a lot of things.
What did the security guard say?
He last saw her
while making his rounds at 10:00 p.m.
He didn't see anyone suspicious.
[breathes deeply]
- There you go.
- [students] Thank you.
- [vendor] Bye.
- Hello.
[♪ jaunty music playing]
[softly] Oh...
PIZZA, SPICY
LOW SUGAR CUSTARD, RED BEAN
Excuse me, what's the "custard" flavor?
It's filled with custard cream.
Oh!
Then I'll take four of each flavor.
Coming right up.
NO CARD, CASH ONLY
BANK TRANSFER DETAILS
Don't you take card?
You can pay by bank transfer.
- Bank transfer?
- [vendor] Yes.
Bank transfer.
[♪ music fades]
I'm sure Moon Seyeon died
because of the curse.
[student] That curse was real.
You think that girl really killed her?
Why else did she die in the practice room?
What do you mean?
A curse?
- Girls.
- Here, all packed up for you.
- Please transfer the money.
- Right, bank transfer.
Girls!
Don't go.
I'll buy you custard bungeoppang!
[sighs]
By the way,
the students said something weird.
Like what?
That Seyeon died from a curse.
- A curse?
- [Isoo] Yeah.
They said she was cursed
and died in the practice room.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Mmm.
Personally,
I prefer red bean.
[♪ jaunty music playing]
I'm trying to be serious here.
- I prefer custard.
- [Kyungjin, muffled] I prefer red bean.
Really?
[♪ music fades]
SEWON HOSPITAL
[footsteps approaching]
[Dr. Jinkyung] Hello.
[chuckles]
It's been a while.
Hello.
Did you have chemotherapy?
- Yes.
- [chuckles softly]
How are you feeling?
Much better, thanks to you.
I'm glad to hear that.
I thought you were sitting here
because you weren't feeling well.
I was just
thinking I might live
a little differently from now on.
Differently? In what way?
I originally planned to retire
last year and travel the world.
Travel the world?
It's nothing grand,
but I've only ever
traveled abroad for work.
[♪ melancholy music playing]
Ah, you must've led quite a busy life.
[chuckles]
Traveling the world.
That sounds nice.
I'm actually starting
my sabbatical next month.
I was thinking of taking a trip, too.
Sabbatical?
That's nice.
I can't even remember the last time
I did nothing and just relaxed.
[sighs deeply] Time really flies,
doesn't it? [chuckles]
- It does.
- [chuckles]
[♪ melancholy music continues]
[breath trembles] My daughter
got divorced when Seyeon was little,
then passed away young.
So I raised Seyeon on my own.
[sniffles, breathes deeply]
She was such a sweet and lovely girl.
Ever since she was little,
whenever she heard any music,
she would dance beautifully
like a fairy, like an angel.
She said she'd become a famous dancer...
[voice shaking] ...and take good care
of her grandma. [sobbing]
As her grandmother, I had no money,
no power.
[sniffles]
Even though that poor child was sick,
she worked part-time
while going to school.
Was she unwell?
She had asthma.
[breath trembling]
But she still went to practice every day
and even got the lead role
in the arts festival.
How could this happen? [sobbing]
Could we look around Seyeon's room?
Yes.
- [continues sobbing]
- [door opens]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[♪ pulsating foreboding music playing]
AWARD CERTIFICATE
I CURSE YOU, MOON SEYEON
DIE, DIE!
Look at this.
[♪ music increases in tempo]
Is this the curse?
[Hyera] Do you know what this is?
What's this?
It was in her desk drawer.
[Grandma, gasps shakily] Did someone
hate my granddaughter this much?
[sobbing] Why?
[♪ music swells]
SEOUL GANGHA POLICE STATION
[♪ music fades]
[♪ quirky, dramatic music playing]
[Kyungjin] Hey!
[laughing maniacally]
What's with him?
[Kyungjin continues laughing maniacally]
His girlfriend dumped him.
[in English] What?
Apparently,
it's a first for him.
[in Korean] How did a dating expert
get dumped?
Nobody
- can bat a thousand.
- [cell phone vibrating]
[Isoo exhales deeply]
Hello, Jiwon?
[♪ music fades]
- Did something happen?
- No, it's nothing.
- Did you find anything?
- Not yet.
I played it back from 9:00 p.m.,
but no one went into the building.
[Isoo] You need to look carefully,
Kyungjin.
Our suspect is hiding deep in the shadows.
What?
Remember the Han Yura case? The candles.
The candles.
The key to this case is the curse.
A vengeful presence might've been
caught on camera. Play it.
[scoffs softly]
[keyboard clacking]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
Okay, I'll call you later.
[♪ music fades]
When's the autopsy?
They're just starting now.
[♪ gripping, foreboding music playing]
[Dr. Yoon, sighs] One second.
[camera shutter clicking]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
Do we have a time of death?
Between 10:00 and 11:00 p.m.
[sighs heavily]
Then we can't rule out the security guard.
[both gasp]
[♪ music fades]
[Isoo gasps softly]
- Did you see that?
- Yes.
What is it now?
It's real.
Here, look.
[♪ ominous music playing]
See? Right here.
Three, two, one.
[♪ ominous sting]
[♪ music fades]
[Isoo exhales sharply]
[sniffles]
It's probably a reflection.
Yeah, like the shadow of a tree.
How is this the shadow of a tree?
- It's dust. There's dust on the camera.
- Yeah, she's right.
Hey, what kind of ghost
shows up on camera?
Don't you know about spirit photography?
What kind of dust is that big?
This looks way too much like a person.
That's enough.
I don't know
how that got caught on camera,
but no ghost or curse can kill a person.
How can you be so sure?
The truth is out there.
[♪ upbeat, jaunty music playing]
Someone's vengeful spirit
is haunting the school.
A haunted arts school.
[breath trembling, grunts]
I'm scared.
[♪ music fades]
[gasps softly]
Is it really dust?
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
You found this inside Seyeon's desk?
[exhales in disbelief]
Who would do such a thing?
Someone despised Moon Seyeon.
Does anyone come to mind?
[exhales softly]
[breathes deeply] I really don't know.
Mmm, then do you know
who Seyeon's closest friend was?
[♪ suspenseful, pulsating music playing]
[Hyera] We heard you were close to Seyeon.
THIRD-YEAR DANCE STUDENT
PARK DAHYE
We had something to ask you.
Okay.
This was inside Seyeon's desk.
[♪ music fades]
Who do you think sent it?
Anyone come to mind?
You can be honest. It'll stay between us.
There was an accident a week ago.
[♪ soft, suspenseful music playing]
- An accident?
- [Dahye] Yes.
Hayun fell and broke her arm.
[grunts, groans]
[whimpers]
[groans, breathes heavily]
[Dahye] I heard that Seyeon was behind it.
Did Seyeon really push her?
She said it wasn't her,
but apparently, everyone saw it.
THIRD-YEAR DANCE STUDENT
KIM HAYUN
Hayun, can you show us your arm?
You're hurt.
How did that happen?
I just fell.
We heard Seyeon pushed you.
Is that why you sent this to her?
What's this?
I don't do stuff like this.
Is it true that Seyeon pushed you?
Yes.
Why did she do it?
She can't even dance,
but she got cocky about getting the lead,
so I said something.
What did you say?
I asked if she'd bribed the principal.
What do you mean?
There were always rumors about that.
About how the principal's
obsessed with money.
If she wasn't paid off,
why would she pick Seyeon to be the lead?
This wasn't me.
Song Gaeun's the one
who'd do something so immature.
She's the one who really hated Seyeon.
THIRD-YEAR DANCE STUDENT
SONG GAEUN
[Isoo] Try opening it.
[♪ suspenseful music continues]
It was you.
Why did you send this?
Because I was pissed off.
Based on talent, I should be the lead.
But this is just something everyone does.
Do you think the principal favored Seyeon?
Isn't that obvious?
She really wasn't talented.
Why would she favor Seyeon?
How would I know?
But Seyeon told me
the principal has no choice
but to pick her for the lead.
[♪ suspenseful, ticking music playing]
In any case,
this case has nothing to do with me.
She didn't die because of this note.
Why did you write that you curse her?
People don't usually say that.
And what's this paper?
I bought it at the Witch's Shop.
It's a trend at school.
Because of Baek Yuna.
Baek Yuna?
An upperclassman
who killed herself last year.
Someone killed herself here?
Yes, in the practice room.
That's why all the girls are saying
that Baek Yuna killed Seyeon.
Were they connected somehow?
I wouldn't know.
[♪ gripping, suspenseful music playing]
[camera shutter clicking]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[forensics officer] What is all this?
[♪ music swells, fades]
VICTIM, CRIME SCENE, PRACTICE ROOM
We responded to the scene
in the Baek Yuna case.
Was that the ghost of Baek Yuna?
Ghost?
At this school,
Baek Yuna's ghost is
still wandering around.
What's wrong with you?
How did she die?
It was a suicide.
She cut an artery
in the practice room late at night.
[♪ tense music playing]
Any chance it was a murder?
No one was on site
except the security guard.
Ah, and the practice room was locked.
What about security cameras?
That's the problem.
They were down.
Why did she commit suicide?
[inhales deeply]
That's also a bit unclear,
but she was on antidepressants
a month or two before the incident.
Having said that,
she did text her mother
before committing suicide.
It said she was sorry.
MOM, I'M SORRY
Were there rumors
that the principal was taking bribes?
Yes, there were.
The principal used to be a famous dancer,
but she quit because of a slipped disc
and returned to her old school.
There was talk that she loved
designer goods and bribes.
How is that related to Baek Yuna's case?
We looked into it.
According to the rumors,
Baek Yuna's mother was the one
who bribed the principal.
Baek Yuna's mother bribed the principal?
Wait,
she became the lead of the festival
after bribing the principal
and had a promising future,
so why did she kill herself?
[♪ music fades]
"I curse you."
I CURSE YOU
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
Was that about Seyeon?
VICTIM, MOON SEYEON, AGE 18
I CURSE YOU, MOON SEYEON
DIE, DIE!
[forensics officer] Detective Joo.
I found something strange.
We're still investigating
the contents that were inside.
I bought it at the Witch's Shop.
It's a trend at school.
We need to meet this witch.
[♪ music fades]
- [toy skeleton chimes]
- Jesus Christ!
What on earth?
[♪ eerie, suspenseful music playing]
[owner, in deep voice] Welcome.
OWNER OF THE WITCH'S SHOP
MA HYUNYOUNG
Do you wish to curse someone?
Or know the future?
In this place, you can do it all.
- [clip clicks]
- We're police.
[in normal voice] Gosh,
what brings the police here? [chuckles]
Everything in here might look strange,
but it's just the shop's theme.
They're all just toys. Like this.
[♪ quirky music playing]
A student from
Juyeon Arts High School recently died.
This was among her belongings.
How did she die?
- We're still investigating that.
- [♪ music fades]
- What is this?
- That's...
It's just a way to blow off some steam.
It's really nothing.
Uh, is this a real bone?
[scoffs]
Oh, of course not. It's plastic.
Where would I get real bones?
Yeah, I thought as much.
But do students buy a lot of this stuff?
Business isn't exactly booming,
but a lot of Juyeon Arts students
have been coming since last year.
They buy curse charms
and protective charms.
Mmm.
I'll buy one of these, too.
Sure.
Excuse me.
I need a copy
of your shop's security footage.
[Hyunuong] Sure.
Sorry, but...
this is
my fifth store.
I really can't afford
to go out of business. [chuckles]
You should try changing your theme.
You're too sweet-looking
for a gloomy place like this.
[♪ quirky music playing]
- Should I?
- [Isoo] Yes.
This "Good Luck" charm.
I'll buy ten of these.
[gasps]
Gosh, my Flex Cop! [squeals]
- [Isoo] You know me?
- [Hyunuong] Of course I do.
There's no other chaebol this handsome.
Can you sign your autograph here, too?
- On this?
- It's a curse charm. My bad.
[Isoo] Seriously, on a curse charm?
[Hyunuong] I can't let you get cursed.
- I need a pen.
- Right, a pen. [giggles]
[Isoo, softly] Honestly.
[♪ music fades]
JUYEON ARTS HIGH SCHOOL ARTS FESTIVAL D-6
I know you're all having a hard time
after what happened to Seyeon.
However,
the arts festival
must go ahead as planned.
It's also the right thing
to do for Seyeon.
So you must pull yourselves together
and keep practicing.
[all] Yes, ma'am.
You know who's coming
to the festival, don't you?
Deans from arts colleges,
and even the Minister
of Culture, Sports and Tourism.
Your futures depend on this.
The lead dancer will be...
[♪ suspenseful piano music playing]
...Song Gaeun.
[♪ music turns ominous]
You can do it, right, Gaeun?
Yes, ma'am.
[♪ music fades]
NATIONAL FORENSIC SERVICE
[exhales sharply]
[muttering]
Jiwon!
What are you doing?
Oh.
Experimenting.
What?
Ah...
Look at this.
[♪ gripping, suspenseful music playing]
These wounds
don't look like cuts from a blade.
The skin tore when the blade struck her.
This is the same kind of blade
the victim used.
The edge isn't sharp.
The blade didn't cut her.
It struck her and tore her skin.
But the angle seemed a little odd,
so I was trying it out myself.
See?
It looks the same, right?
Uh...
- Then...
- Yes.
She did this to herself.
Given the angle,
it was self-inflicted.
- [blunt thudding]
- [screaming]
Can someone die from wounds like these?
No.
The victim had asthma.
An asthma attack narrowed her airways,
which deprived her of oxygen.
That led to cardiac arrest.
Also, we found
an unidentified metabolite in her blood,
but we need to look into that further.
Okay.
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
PARK JUNYOUNG
INCOMING CALL
[Junyoung, over car audio] Hey, are you
with Detective Joo?
Yes, go ahead.
The autopsy results are out.
She went into cardiac arrest
from an asthma attack.
[Isoo] What?
What about the cuts on her legs?
They seem self-inflicted.
She did that to herself? Why?
[Junyoung] I don't know,
but the angle suggests
she struck herself and the skin tore.
They also found an unusual metabolite.
They'll analyze it and let us know.
Okay, great job.
Okay.
[Hyera] Wait, Detective Park.
Can you check Baek Yuna's case again?
Start with the security guard.
The security cameras keep bothering me.
- [Junyoung] Okay, got it.
- [line disconnects]
Did Baek Yuna really curse Moon Seyeon?
[♪ tense music playing]
Turn the car around.
I need to see the principal.
What am I, your chauffeur?
You can turn around there.
Yes, ma'am, all right.
[engine revs]
[♪ music fades]
JUYEON ARTS HIGH SCHOOL
[Juhee] Yuna...
was such a promising student.
You don't know how heartbroken I was
when she died like that.
Why would she have taken her own life?
I don't know.
She did seem a little depressed
from before the incident,
but no matter how much I asked,
she wouldn't tell me.
We heard there were rumors
that Baek Yuna's mother gave you a bribe.
[sighs wearily]
[inhales] That's a misunderstanding.
It was a donation for the arts festival,
but people who like to gossip
spread those ridiculous rumors.
What about Seyeon?
The students believe
you received a bribe from her.
[sighs softly, inhales]
They're too young to know any better.
You see, Seyeon
came from a low-income family.
She also had asthma,
so she had a hard time
practicing with the other students.
She had a lot of potential,
so I picked her as the lead dancer
and allowed her to practice on her own.
What happened to Seyeon?
It seems she died from an asthma attack.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
We came to tell you
that this wasn't a murder.
[exhales sharply]
Then what happened to her legs?
[Isoo] Mmm.
That
might be Baek Yuna's curse.
Uh, this is just my unofficial opinion.
What are you talking about?
[inhales sharply] This school
is filled with the energy of a curse.
Uh...
What's this?
Have you never seen it before?
It's a trend among the students.
It's a curse pouch.
The students carry this around?
No.
They secretly slip the curse in.
My gosh, how could they do such a thing?
[exhales softly]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[♪ music turns ominous]
SONG GAEUN
[intercom chimes]
Oh.
I'm with Gangha Police.
You remember me, right?
Yes.
May I come in for a second?
Sure.
Did I do something wrong?
Uh, a student died
at school last fall, right?
Yes.
Back then,
- why did you do it?
- What?
[♪ tense, suspenseful music playing]
Why did you do it?
Because I was scared.
Of what?
I was the only person at school.
I was worried I'd become a suspect.
It's not too late.
[♪ tense, pulsating music playing]
Tell me everything
right from the beginning.
At night, the student's mother turned up,
saying her daughter was missing.
SEVEN MONTHS AGO
[exclaims in horror]
[sobbing]
[security guard] But she was dead.
The police came
and asked for the security footage,
but the cameras were off.
So,
I lied
that they'd been down for a few days.
But I thought it was a suicide.
It's hard to say now.
You said the cameras weren't down.
Someone turned them off.
I mean,
I don't know if they were turned off
or if I pressed the wrong button.
I was still new to the job back then.
I swear, no one was there.
When did you realize the cameras were off?
I found out after the police arrived,
so it was near midnight.
When did you last see them on?
I went to do my rounds at 10:00 p.m.,
and they were working fine then.
[♪ music swells, fades]
[sighs softly]
[♪ gripping, suspenseful music playing]
If someone turned off
the security cameras...
Was Baek Yuna murdered?
Any luck reaching Baek Yuna's parents?
No. They both moved abroad,
and I can't get a hold of them.
[breathes deeply]
Let's focus on Moon Seyeon's case first.
Okay.
But this seems like an accident,
not a crime.
- We'll have to find out.
- How?
- I know an expert.
- [♪ music fades]
- Kyungjin, let's go.
- Okay.
[door opens]
[♪ gripping, suspenseful music playing]
You're asking if this is a real curse?
- Yes.
- [shaman] Mmm.
- [bells jangling]
[♪ music fades]
It's not.
This poor child
is no longer in this world.
She has already left.
Ah. Then what about this student?
Another one died?
Yes, another student died
in the exact same place.
[sighs deeply]
[bells jangling]
[♪ eerie, suspenseful music playing]
[screeching eerily]
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music resumes tempo]
She's still at the school.
A vengeful spirit is there.
[grunts softly]
[♪ percussive folk music playing]
[spectral exhale]
[♪ eerie, suspenseful music continues]
- [shaman] What is that?
- [spectral exhale]
[♪ music turns ominous]
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
[exhales softly]
What is it?
An item with fur, about this big.
She left it behind.
[whispering] What could it be?
Why is your mind so troubled?
[chuckles]
You got dumped by a girl.
[Kyungjin gasps]
How did you know?
Call her. She's waiting for you.
What? Right now?
Are you going to let
a good woman get away?
No.
[Isoo chuckles]
[shaman] Detective Jin.
Yes?
I have a feeling something bad
is going to happen soon.
- To me?
- Yes.
[♪ melancholy music playing]
Misfortune and trouble
with the law await you.
I see blood.
Be careful.
Someone is after you.
You mustn't open the door.
[♪ music fades]
[♪ gentle, melancholy music playing]
[exhales softly]
[sighs heavily]
[sighs softly]
[grunts]
[♪ pleasant music plays, fades]
[birds chirping]
[sighs softly]
[♪ ominous music playing]
[♪ ticking, ominous music playing]
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
[cell phone vibrating]
Mmm.
- Hello?
- [Isoo] Doctor.
I just woke up and my house is a wreck.
[sighs] I don't remember anything
about this.
Does the medication I'm on
have any side effects?
[psychiatrist] No, the medication
you're currently taking is very safe.
You might feel a little dizzy,
but there are no serious side effects.
Could a burglar have broken in?
No. No one can get in here.
And nothing's been stolen.
- Would you like to come in to see me?
- Yes, all right.
[line disconnects]
[♪ ominous music playing]
[♪ music fades]
Hey, Detective Joo.
Have a look at this.
This red thing here.
It's a drug.
[♪ tense, suspenseful music playing]
- A drug?
- Yes.
I've never seen it before.
Narcotics are looking into it.
- I'll let you know once I know more.
- Okay.
- Take care.
[line connects, ringing]
[Dr. Yoon] Hello?
That metabolite found
in Moon Seyeon's blood.
Ah.
The lab results came back.
- It's a drug.
- What kind of drug is it?
[sighs] I think this is the first time
it's turned up in Korea.
You know that case overseas
when someone was paralyzed
- after touching a bill on the ground?
- Yes.
It's a similar kind of drug.
It causes hallucinations in most people,
but the victim had asthma,
so it triggered an attack.
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
There was a drug?
[Hyera] Yes.
Someone slipped this drug
into Seyeon's bag...
[♪ gripping, suspenseful music playing]
...and it made her hallucinate.
That triggered an asthma attack
and she died.
Did someone put this drug in to kill her?
It might have been
to take the lead role from her.
They might not have known
it was dangerous for someone with asthma.
They put a curse pouch in her bag?
It must've happened at school.
Yes.
The culprit would've left a trace.
- Call in a drug-sniffing dog.
- Got it.
[♪ music fades]
[bag unzips]
[♪ tense, foreboding music playing]
[breathes heavily]
- [♪ ominous sting]
- [♪ tense, foreboding music continues]
[exhales shakily]
[Juhee] Good morning.
Is everyone here?
All right, get into formation.
[♪ tense, foreboding music continues]
[brakes squeal]
All right.
Get ready!
[♪ music fades]
[♪ tense, suspenseful music playing]
[blade swooshing]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[barking]
[♪ music resumes tempo]
[high-pitched tone droning, fades]
[blade swooshing]
[spectral breathing]
[♪ music swells]
[Gaeun panting]
[♪ music fades]
[panting, breath trembling]
- [stick taps twice]
- What are you doing?
[Gaeun, breath trembling]
Gaeun, what's wrong?
[breathing frantically]
[breathing slowing, trembling]
[♪ ominous music playing]
[spectral breathing]
[Seyeon] I'm the lead dancer.
[slow, heavy, distorted breathing]
- [Yuna] I'm the lead dancer.
- [Seyeon] I'm the lead dancer.
[spectral murmuring]
[♪ music swells]
[distorted screaming]
[sharp swoosh, slash]
[♪ music slows]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[Gaeun breathing heavily, distorted]
[♪ music increases in tempo]
[♪ music swells]
[♪ music fades]
FLEX X COP 2
EPISODE 9
WHAT'S THE TRUTH BEHIND THE CURSE?
[♪ upbeat pop music playing,
Hersh "Shadows In The Night"]
Special Cast. Joo Hyunyoung
Special Cast. Jeon Hyebin
A curse pouch had drugs inside.
[Juhee] Are you saying one of my students
did something like that?
Can we talk for a moment?
Where would I get drugs?
[Hyera] Did you find anything
on Seyeon's phone?
[shaman] An item with fur, about this big.
The shaman said she saw this.
This is a video app.
You can't do this.
- [students gasp]
- [Hayun] I was only messing around.
But how did you know?
Let's do this!
Did Isoo side with Joo Hyera?
[Minjae] Yu Seongwon brought a woman over.
- [Hyera] We have no way of watching him.
- [car horn honking]
What was the worst thing you've ever done?
What about you?
The worst thing I've done?
You'd be shocked if you knew.
How do you want to die?
[♪ music fades]
Why do you take photographs?
To feel you while I work.
[♪ foreboding music playing]
Can I get a copy if they come out well?
[chuckles softly]
No.
What kind of artwork
are you going to make me into?
I'm not sure. [sighs softly]
I can't say I know you yet.
What do you like most?
I like painting the most.
I wish I could
spend just one month painting,
without worrying about money.
[scoffs]
That's no fun.
What's no fun?
[exhales softly]
Want a glass of champagne?
Translated by Hyesoo Lee